844 E 100 S, Salt Lake City, 84102 sam_evans1986@hotmail.com (801) 931-1430

SAMUEL EVANS

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated Full-Stack Web Developer with ~1 year of experience. A team player with a strong problem-solving ability and a keen eye for detail. Adaptable to changing technologies and environments. Ready to contribute to the success of any organization by leveraging my skills and expertise.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

MAR, 2023 - AUG, 2023

Account representative, Sutter Physican Services, Salt Lake City

- Accounts receivable
- Claim resolution
- Team collaboration
- · Creating training documents

SEP, 2018 - AUG, 2019

Patient Representative, University of Utah, Salt Lake City

- · Assisted with patient account reconciliation
- · Collaborated with team members to address business needs
- · Resolved payment issues for patients

FEB, 2020 - PRESENT

Pre-auth Clerk, Myriad Genetics, Remote

- · Requesting records to assist in pre-authorizations
- · Creating training documents and training new team members
- Data entry
- Claim resolution

EDUCATION

JUN, 2004 - PRESENT

High School Diploma, VALLEY HIGH SCHOOL, SANDY, AS

JUN, 2023 - PRESENT

Web development certification, University of Utah, Salt Lake City

Expecting to finish the program by Dec of 2023. Studies include full stack development with the following technologies HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, Web API server/client, NodeJs, MySQL, NoSQL, Express, Reactjs, Bootstrap.

CJ PEDERSEN

SUTTER PHYSICIAN SERVICES & (801) 694-7178

REFERENCES

JOSH WILLIAMS

GREENTHREAD HERBS

☑ joshwagandha@gmail.com

⟨801⟩ 918-2824

VANESSA WHITEHEAD

SUTTER PHYSICIAN SERVICES

⟨801⟩ 706-2359

LINKS

Github

LinkedIn

SKILLS

Multitasking

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Problem Solving

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Collaboration

••••

Strong Communication Skills

••••

VS code

•••00

Javascript

•••00

CSS

•••00

React

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$